From now on, mom and dad
will be in your care
What
You mean
you're dumping them on us
and washing your hands of them
Don't put it that way
It's not that I don't care
I just have no money
How about you pay off my loan shark debt
and buy back my house
Then without a word
I'll take them and leave
and never bother you again
How about that
If you're trying to use this
to force me to pay your debts
then you're dead wrong
If you don't pay
mom and dad will live with you
You can't just watch them
starve to death with me
Lewes
Cynthia
We can't count on Daniel
I don't ask for much
just some food for your dad and me
and a place to stay
Lewes
We won't eat for free
Your mom and I can still work
Feed the forest frogs
We can clean up too
Please don't kick us out
They're his in-laws after all
He can't just ignore them
Daniel is a bit unreliable
but he can't watch the elders starve
Lewes is rich now
Supporting two elders is no big deal
Lewes
Mom, Dad
What are you saying
We won't make you work
A son-in-law is half a son
It's my duty to support you
It worked
As long as they stay at the farm
they can definitely steal the formula
I knew Lewes was a dutiful son
He wouldn't abandon us
Cynthia
Go ask the village chief
who has a house for rent
Rent a house for them
and buy some meat and veggies
Let them stay peacefully in the village
I'll cover their living expenses
Back to the village
No way